



Cardoso De Alencar Cristhofer

Male, 23 years, born on 21 October 1994

+7 (904) 3397012 — preferred means of communication • Personal phone number

cristhofer-alencar@hotmail.com Skype: cristhofer alencar

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/cristhoferalencar Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/cristhofer.alencar Free-lance: https://www.fl.ru/users/Cristhofer Al

Reside in: Saint Petersburg, m. Akademicheskaya Citizenship: Brazil, work permit at: Russia, Brazil

Ready to relocate: Other countries, ready for business trips

Desired position and salary

Web Developer 80 000 **RUB**

IT, Internet, Telecom

- Software Development
- Web Engineer
- · Web master

Employment: work placement, volunteering, part time, project work, full time

Work schedule: flexible schedule, full day, shift schedule, rotation based work, remote

working

Desired travel time to work: any

Work experience — 6 years

January 2015 — December 2017 3 years

J.A Produtos Naturais

Brazil

IT manager and Development leader

- -Plan and develop 3 web systems, as well as the virtual shop, currently in use.
- -Update and support the systems and virtual shop, as well as the internal server.
- -Promoted to IT manager and development leader.

January 2012 — December 2015 4 years

Fenix WebMaster

Brazil

Web developer

Design and Develop Web Sites

January 2014 — December 2014 1 year

Agência Colmeia

Brazil

Web developer

- -Design and Develop Web Sites and Systems.
- -Provide support and updates on already designed sites and systems.

Education

Master

2019

St. Petersburg State Polytechnic University, Saint Petersburg

Information Systems, Applied Informatics (by area)

²⁰¹⁶ Faculdade de Juazeiro do Norte

Information Science, Information Systems

Professional development, courses

2016 Work Series, PHP Orientado a Objetos

Upinside, Web Development

Key skills

Languages Portuguese — native

English — I am a fluent speaker Spanish — I am a fluent speaker Russian — basic knowledge

Skills PHP HTML JavaScript MySQL CSS jQuery Git HTML5

Joomla CMS Bootstrap CMS Wordpress SEO Ajax MVC SQL

Английский язык португальский язык ООП

Further information

About me

Hello, my name is Cristhofer Alencar and I'm from Brazil. Currently, I'm a scholarship fellow in the master's degree program at the Polytechnic University of St. Petersburg in Russia. I came to Russia seeking a new challenge to develop myself, and now I feel that is time to put my skills to good use. I'm looking for the opportunity to work in a good company where I can contribute to its development and develop myself. In my curriculum, you can find complete information about me, but I would like to highlight a few: I'm a Web Developer with over 5 years of experience in web technologies and always willing to learn more, I like to travel a lot so I'm always open to new opportunities to work and travel, I am fluent in English, Portuguese, Spanish and Russian, in an agreement with the company I have permission to work in Russia according to Russian laws, I also have experience with systems maintenance, support and development and eager to learn everything that your company has to offer me.